We are back.
And if you've not watched one of these
videos before, this is where I
roast people constructively from their
Instagram and sales funnel process.
This is what I do for a living.
I'm just going to show you behind the
scenes.
In the link in the description,
you can click that,
and you can give me your
details so I can add them to the roast.
I have got Claude to pick 20 people at
random from the last video, and we're
going to go through their stuff.
Beginning with Kashan Qatar.
Some of them will be just absolute dog
shit, but okay.
Kasha Qatar? Kash Actor, Kash Act.
ACL, meniscus, cartilage.
Do you know what? I like this.
I like that straight away I'm thinking
even though he hasn't said much about it,
already I'm interested. These
are probably what?
The three most devastating knee injuries.
There's my pain point straight away.
Already, boom. Expert guidance on knees,
health, and wellness.
Consultant, knee surgeon, educator,
health innovator.
Okay,
I think we're a little bit repetitive on
this. View's not mine.
Cleveland Clinic London. Perfect.
I would like to clean this up a little
bit, but knee surgeon or knee
expert, just love that. It's very good.
We've got 47,000 followers,
big fan of that.
And out of 767 posts,
it's pretty good ratios.
So already I can see some high-quality
content here.
Let's get into some and see what we think.
pain and injuries, you're not alone.
I'm Dr.
Kash Aktar, consultant knee surgeon,
associate professor.
Meniscus repair or meniscectomy.
Okay.
What's the difference,
and why do we choose one over the other?
Let's break it down. A meniscus-
The one thing that straight away I pick
from there is someone that I would say I
know knees relatively well.
I don't know what the second thing is that
you've said. So if I
was to watch this browsing,
I would think that this is a
conversation too high level for me
and I could leave.
So ultimately, let's see
if I can start this one again.
Meniscus repair or meniscectomy.
What's the difference,
and why do we choose one over the other?
Maybe your hook could be,
if you've injured your meniscus, what
is the best way to
treat it?
Then we could get into the setup.
There are two main ways
that you can deal with a meniscus tear.
You can do the meniscus repair
or something called a meniscectomy, which
is... And you want to break it down.
I always think it's important
that we dumb down the level of content as
if we're
talking to a 12-year-old.
Not because people are stupid,
but because we want
everyone to understand. Like I say,
when I see that down there, I think, oh,
is this for surgeons?
Some meniscus tears heal, most don't.
Let me tell you why.
Okay, good hook. Let me think.
I'm Kash Aktar, consultant knee surgeon.
Think of the menis-
The
introduction part, I don't know
if we need that in every reel.
We'll see if it is.
People are going to figure this out
because they're going to watch three,
four of
your videos.
And if you're saying it in every video,
could we just put that in the
bio?
Meniscus in three zones.
The outer third has some blood supply.
That's the red zone.
If you tear the meniscus there, it might-
Would say the music
is a little bit overpowering.
Look, you're an authority.
You're well lit.
Everything's perfect here.
You're even using professional audio.
Let's not hinder that. Like right now,
for this video, there is no external
audio. There's no jingles or whatever.
I'm trying to educate.
And I think if you're trying to educate
like me, maybe we just don't need that.
7,000 likes is incredible though.
Deal with the rest,
or sometimes it needs surgical repair.
The middle third,
known as the red-white zone,
has limited blood supply.
These tears have some healing potential,
especially if they're repaired early and
well-supported and protected.
But the inner third,
that's the white-white zone,
that's completely avascular.
No blood supply means-
Okay. Now,
although this has performed really well,
I think that potentially
you have a habit.
So in the nutrition space,
some people have come from a
university lecturing standpoint,
and they can labor their point because
they have
one hour to do so.
I think a little bit here,
you've done quite a lot of
consultancy where you've got someone in a
room and you're talking to them.
If possible, let's just try
and get to those points a little bit
quicker.
I want you to think that everyone there
is ADHD as fuck.
But again, I really like this.
But imagine this, case in point, right
now, I've got other people to look at,
other things to do.
I had to stop the video so we could move
on.
I don't think I've learned the point
that you're talking about just yet.
Just realized I'm wearing this hat
and I look like a...
I need people's help, please.
I hope you're having a blessed Sabbath.
Enjoy the Sunday, whatever you're doing.
And if-
So these bits here,
although to your followers it's going to
be
fantastic,
I'm not sure we're establishing quite
early on what
the video is about, which could be fine.
An ACL tear does not just affect the ACL.
If the knee stays unstable,
it can start damaging the meniscus too.
Okay. Again,
we're coming in with some evidence here.
I don't think our hook
was strong enough here.
And I'm not saying hook like we need to
bait people into it,
but you're referencing
a study and you could just say,
some people live their life without fixing
their
ACL. This new study says
that could be a problem.
Now straight away within those few
seconds,
I fully understand what we're going to
get into and this means anyone
that wants to understand more can stay,
anyone else
can leave.
If you leave an ACL deficient knee
unstable for too long, the medial
meniscus often pays the price.
Okay,
and that's exactly what I said before,
which is fantastic.
And you'll notice
that this one has performed quite a bit
better than the one
before.
An ACL, if you leave it-
If anything, it's performed twice as well.
This content is really good.
I really like this.
And I can only imagine that this
is going to benefit the amount
of bookings or people that come to you.
You've established yourself as an
authority. Put it this way.
After doing this,
if I blow an ACL at Roger Gracie's
or ARMA in
the UK, I'm sliding in, bro, and going,
"Hey, fix me up." Okay.
Getting a little bit lost on the website
as far as I'm on here, I'm not really
sure what it is you're selling, which
is going to be a bit of a problem.
Some homework for you, Kash.
I'm sure you've got one in the office,
the anatomy of the knee,
and I want you to actually do some real
basic stuff.
What is the ACL joint? What
are the levels of tear?
Why is it important for stability?
I then also would probably want a little
bit more
education around recovery times,
procedures.
I would probably like to even know your
opinion about things like peptide use to
heal these. But all in all,
really like this.
So from the top,
let's make this a little bit more clear.
If you need to repeat something in every
reel, let's just put it in here so we
don't have to.
And those first few seconds,
let's just think about what
the audience are really keen to know.
But that was really good for a first one.
Okay.
Already I've spotted a problem with this
next one. Okay.
Tayce Travis, you look like a boss girl,
Siren Strength Collective. Now,
I think your brand already, and I've not
even looked, is actually Tayce Travis.
I
reckon I'm going to watch your stuff.
I just think you're going to be the brand
straight away.
I don't think anyone is out there going,
"Oh my god, you need to follow the Siren
Strength Collective." They're going to go,
"Oh, Tayce. She's absolute legend.
Let's get into some of your stuff." I feel
like this one could've been a bit more
of you just saying, "Hey, guys.
If you've ever struggled with your
chin-ups, this
one simple tip made it a lot easier for
me.
If you pull up with your elbows,
not your hands, boom." Again, I think
that just
would've done a lot better because I want
to get to know you, Tayce.
[singing] Child I will-
I feel like you've just got footage of a
movement.
You've tried to slap another thing about
protein in there.
These don't make sense.
You're about to do an Olympic lift.
Where the hell does protein come in?
Gosh,
I just want to go to the gym to lift some
weight and just to
tone up.
I'm just here for that hourglass physique.
See, look,
you've got good energy about you.
Now,
I'm not sure we quite nailed the hook
here, but you're built for
camera. You're built to present.
You're looking nice. Your hair looks good.
This is the person I want to see on
content.
I used to think my best years
were behind me.
And honestly,
I was so intimidated by the weights
section.
I thought I'd get hurt or
that everyone was watching me.
Cool. Following a script. I like this.
Really good.
But I decided to start small
and just focus on consistency.
Okay, if we're going to go to this
and do these lifts, which is great,
I would love
if we could turn this narrative about
that person.
If you say you thought your best years
were behind you, is age the limiting
factor here?
Let's talk about someone else's age.
So you say Fit Over 35 as a hashtag,
but that should be your hook.
I'm over 35,
and I thought the best years of my lifting
were behind me, but
it turns out they're not. If anything,
I'm the strongest I've ever been, I'm the
best I've ever felt,
and age only just continues to benefit my
lifting
journey. Now the payoff
is going to be how you can transfer
that to the person
watching to make them feel good about
themselves or maybe inclined to work with
you. Because look-
Put my tunes on
...
you're a badass bitch lifting big ass
weights.
You're moving well, chucking up weight,
looking good. We should play into that.
Because when women
are going to watch your content,
they're not really thinking
about you,
they're thinking about themselves.
And if you can be the motivator
and the person that they need to transform
who
they are to do something closer to you,
that's why I think we go with that.
If you've been abusing banded strict
pull-ups and still not improving, yeah,
they're not fixing it.
Don't like the hook.
If you've been abusing banded chin-ups.
No one woke up today going, "Oh,
I've been abusing that band."
You don't need more bands.
You need better progressions.
That was your hook.
Let's have a look at your funnel.
Women 35,
building strength to match ambition.
What does that mean? Women over 30,
building strength
and confidence might have
been better. Fall in love with lifting
and feel good naked. Love that.
Free strength reset guide. Okay,
we've got a lead magnet coming
up. What is a reset guide?
Strength reset guide?
I'm not sure what that is.
If I don't know what it is,
it's going to hinder my
ability to want to click.
So there's an issue I have with it.
I don't think anyone sat up in bed this
morning and went, "I need a free strength
reset guide." Whereas if you were like,
"PB in 30 days, free
guide, let's go." And again,
for your demographic, women over 35,
maybe we
go into gym confidence,
maybe we go into first chin-up.
That's just where I'm leaning. By the way,
guys, I'm doing a free three-day
workshop.
There's going to be a link in the
description to that.
All you need to do is sign up.
Over the three days of that event,
we're going to be
looking at contents, leads, and money.
So please do sign up to that.
And if you sign up to put your name in the
mix for this, with the other link in
there, I'll also add you to that webinar.
Free strength audit.
Don't know what that is.
Battle cancer 12-week program.
Don't know what it is.
Coaching by Siren Collective.
I'd rather get coached by you.
Siren Strength Squat Club online program,
website, articles, gallery, and more.
Okay, so I get here,
and there's paralysis of options.
If there was just one thing here,
it'd make my life easier.
You could literally just say,
"Click this." Now, you said there
was a reset or
something. I don't see that.
Let's have a look at a readiness report.
Readiness report.
You sent me to a Google Form.
I'm out of here.
I'm gonzo. Coaching by Siren Collective.
It's a Google Form. Do you know,
if I do want coaching from you, I want to
know what it is, what it costs,
what I get, why I should trust you.
Oh, there's an online program. And again,
look, this program, right?
The road men would say this
is dead breath. This is dead.
We're at £49. What are you giving me?
Is that all I get?
I'm not buying that. So,
I'm loving what's going on on socials,
but that is
where your bottleneck is. I get here,
and everything's just a bit crap.
But good news is, easy to fix,
easy to get on with. I like the cadence.
1,500 followers, 300 posts. This
is looking good.
Let's have a quick look at something.
What I want you to do as part of your
homework is I want you to go through here
and
look at the videos that get you the most
views and double down.
But I do want to see you talk into camera
a bit more.
I want you to see yourself owning
that space. You're jacked. Love to see it.
Okay.
Hi. They get loud for the douche growers.
Your audience like
that wasn't my favorite hook.
In the back. Say what?
But no offense, this weirdness,
get it out more. Why?
Because this is your best performing
video.
Physique inflation is real,
and we do not talk about this enough in
the fitness
space. So many women
are walking around with body dys-
I think you could've just had the camera
there, walked into shot.
And physique inflation
is such an important topic,
but I think we could've done
that better.
We could've had a picture of Brad Pitt in
"Fight Club,"
then we could've had a picture of whoever
and gone, "This is what a physique..." Or
you could pick a female equivalent.
This is what a physique of someone in the
'90s looked like.
This is what a physique is now.
And then you can be like, "This
is called physique
inflation." Boom. That is three times more
effort, 100 times more views. Very good.
Fix the funnel.
I've set myself George the physio.
George the physio.
George Leatherland, pain
and rehab specialist.
I help people in pain build a body they
trust again with treatment and rehab that
works. Get rid of these dashes,
these little arrows.
I don't think we need them.
Online in the link, in-person sessions,
book now button. Sheffield. Okay.
20,000 followers. Not bad.
So that's one thing
that I've found with PTs
is probably don't understand the
recovery side enough.
Music, little bit dramatic,
little bit loud.
Then I get people in,
and they're absolutely beaten up.
And then-
Actually, before loosen here,
I just want to see the tension
in the outside of this glute.
Even if you're recording yourself with a
client, I think you can just take a pause
and put a hook in here.
Right here, hold
See,
because I don't really know what's
happening.
225 likes, not bad,
but I still don't know what's happening
How can what you do,
specifically the dry needling side of
things, are there any
benefits for regular migraine sufferers?
I appreciate it depends person to person.
Yeah.
But when it comes to-
New tonic, Maji. Thank you. Okay,
I feel like this
needs a voiceover, right?
Because there's nothing actually happening
here.
This, I'm sure, is really important.
The Biering-Sorensen test, right?
Never heard of that. Been a PT 10 years.
Why didn't we voiceover this?
I'm doing a two-minute back extension,
and this is
what it actually tells you. This
is actually called the Biering-Sorensen
test, and
you hold it for two minutes,
and you're on the upper range for spinal
extension
endurance.
Research actually links poor scores on
this test or...
Mate,
this wouldn't even need to be sped up.
You just read that script out
and people go, "Oh,
that's really interesting." So
yeah, I feel like we missed that one.
Don't know what's happening.
Unfortunately,
is I need to press into your armpit.
So, get into here, I'm pressing on
that subscap and it should-
Don't know what's happening.
Oh, here we go.
No. Okay, James Smith, first time caller.
No, long time viewer, first time caller.
I don't know what's going on here.
I don't know what's going on.
Rest is not the answer for your chronic
pain. I know it feels logical.
You're in pain, so let's rest it.
But unfortunately-
What pain? So is it back pain, jaw pain,
foot pain,
knee pain, post-injury pain, posture pain?
Give me more, please
If your pain keeps coming back, this
is probably why.
Music too loud. What pain? Okay.
As you're doing these,
because it's getting really
good views, can you just say,
"For anyone watching,
not knowing what the fuck is
going on, let me tell you.
A tight overprotective quad usually
gripping..."
Mate, this is all interesting stuff.
Why am I reading the caption to find out?
You have a mic, you have a camera,
fucking teach me. Come on, brother.
Yeah,
that's what I'd like to see for that.
Do like the way that you've got a delta
here for online and in person. That's it.
Let's have a fucking look. Back to the...
Oh, a little bit busy,
but let's have a look.
Without the guessing, the waiting,
or it coming back.
Can't we just say something like,
"I'm going to get you back to training,
stronger
than you were before you got injured
or got hurt"?
I just don't think this speaks to people
in that physio world.
Back to doing what you love.
Because most people aren't like,
"I miss doing what I
love. I'm finding myself guessing
and I'm waiting and I want
to get back." They're just like, "Mate,
fucking shoulder's killing me.
What have I got to do to sort this?
Don't care, mate.
Whatever money you need,
I'll pay you to sort this fucking shoulder
out." That's
what they're like. So if I'm there going,
"This fucking shoulder is fucked," and I
go,
"Back to doing what you love without the
guessing," I'm like, "Nah, let me find
somewhere else." So I feel like we're just
a little bit off the mark with that.
Okay, Rosalind, Feed My Health. Hmm,
Feed My Health, eh?
No results found. Mr. Dan Ferrari.
Was that because I had the at in there?
Hold on. Oh, what's going on here?
Rosalind, Feed My Health. She blocked me.
Maybe she blocked me. Here they are.
Hell of a transformation
there. Mr. Dan Ferrari.
Helping ambitious men dominate
modern dating. Okay.
Over 100 dates closed.
I don't know if that sounds impressive,
so maybe let's just get rid of that.
My results.
Why do they always treat me as the daddy?
Date went well. Morning view
and breakfast.
At this point, I'm just lazy,
I'm doing dates. What is this?
Love me a girl in leggings,
what can I say? What on earth is this?
Don't know what I'm excited to--
Join my private Telegram.
Is this fucking OnlyF- Oh, my good Lord.
Oh, my Lord.
Is this some fucking OnlyFans stuff,
brother? That's mad. All right,
school.com.
So I feel like I'm watching soft-core porn
back.
The cold approach to blowjob. Hold on.
[hip hop music]
This one. Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
Do you speak English?
Yeah, I do.
I've noticed you walking down there.
I'm literally over there with my friends,
having a few drinks.
Oh, yeah.
But I've just noticed you,
and I couldn't forget about the way you're
just sitting
here in the sun.
Music's a bit mad on that.
But do you know what? I like it.
It's different.
I don't think looksmaxing is a bad thing.
I don't disagree with it.
I think you should go to the gym,
eat good-
Let's have a look over here. All right.
Imagine a place where you learn proven
ways to get hot girls, hang out with
like-minded people, and help each other.
Okay. It's interesting.
We are in a bit of a dating crisis,
I must say. 278 members.
Let's have a little look.
Welcome to the free dating course,
where I will show you how to get hot
girls to fall in love with you without you
needing to be-
Feels like "The Game" by Neil Strauss
... good-looking or rich,
and no matter what your ethnic background
is.
I am going to show you the exact blueprint
that has allowed me to go from this
spotty virgin guy in his bedroom,
around boxes of-
It's a bit like Hamza reincarnated
... pizza, eating pizza every day,
and only having a dog as his-
So this is interesting because I'm pretty
sure, "The Game" really...
Oh, there you go,
"The Game." "The Game" by Neil Strauss
pretty much created a
system for people
which they just believed in,
and whether or not the system
actually worked or not,
it worked because you go up
and you talk to people.
Even if you were to, no offense, Mr.
Dan,
if you were to listen to this guy's stuff
or not, if you were just to cold
approach women, you'd do so much better.
And improve the way you per-
Wow. What on earth?
Your girlfriend will cheat on you
if you ignore this,
the same way she cheated on
her boyfriend with a fa- All right,
you need to watch this because this
is going to
change your life. So this is Ahmed,
one of my clients.
We started to-
I don't think that's Lily Phillips.
Bro,
imagine being an average-looking guy like-
[hip hop music] Okay, right.
I don't think we've got the
content down on lock.
I think we've got the avatar fucking on
lock, right?
But 54 posts, not enough.
The stuff with the blowjobs in the toilet.
Look, that's what everyone wants,
don't get me wrong, but
that's not how we go about it, right?
We allude to that. For instance,
you've got to be a bit classier with this,
and
we've got to get into... Look,
you got a picture with a fit bird
and a cigar,
I get it. But I'm telling you now,
to scale this business, we've got to
dial this back a little bit.
We've got to create a system where the
framework
could be,
let's not call it The Game because we
shouldn't gamify women.
They are not a game. The Game
is really just trying to find
love. It's difficult because men
and women don't talk to each other enough.
Look, let's create a framework
that we can give men to cold approach
women.
The winning isn't a blowjob in the
toilets.
Winning should be the system,
should be talking to people.
So how is this framework,
the cold approach framework?
And really, if you want to win at this,
bro, let's not make success fucking the
chicks or getting pictures of them in
their undies or like...
And again, the thing I don't like there
is the pics of those girls in your
results, they look kind of unsolicited.
They look a little bit like they didn't
know or consent to it.
That's what I have a little bit of a
problem with.
And again,
if you do want to have hanky-panky
pictures, don't put them on your
social media. So there's my first gripe.
But I think this is great.
I think we're going about it wrong.
You want to be like, not, "I'm Dan,
I help men get laid," or whatever.
We should start getting men to modern
approach to have dates.
And also,
can we change what we make winning look
like on here
to being a date?
To being sitting opposite a beautiful
woman having a glass of
wine, not the sexualized version of it.
If you're one of those guys doing NoFap,
you need to stop right now.
Five minutes ago, me and this girl
were complete strangers.
Now we are on a date together.
Let me show you exactly how I did it
Excuse me. Hi. Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
Do you speak English? Yeah, I do.
I've noticed you walking down there.
I'm literally over there with my friends
having-
Okay, because here, this is fantastic,
the cold approach or whatever.
"This very method helped me to allow me to
sleep with 50 hot girls last year."
A few drinks. Oh, yeah.
But I've just noticed you and I couldn't-
You want my
number? Yeah, I want your number.
There are three ways- Your boys,
I think I found-
Relying on looks-
I'm in love with your eyes.
It's incredible.
Ranking ways women-
Okay, the issue is here.
And I'm going to say this.
I've been there, I've done it,
played the games, whatever.
Shagging 50 birds in a year isn't success.
I know it can sound like it. Most dudes,
they're really looking for the
one, for the right woman.
If you fuck 50 women in a year, sure,
fine,
but that shouldn't be the goal.
That should be the consequences of seeking
the
goal. And what I mean by that is this.
My whole life,
I was looking for a woman
that I could be compatible with, have
children with, live with, coexist with.
And the byproducts of looking for
that woman, sure, meant a lot of dates,
and a
lot of those dates,
by the time you're there,
you might as well go through with it
or whatever. There
were a lot of whatever you want to call it
across the years.
But ultimately, I never was like, "Oh,
yeah, fucked 50 girls
this year." That wasn't winning. That
was probably my frustration of trying
to find love. So again,
the reason I'm spending so long on this
one is we're so
close to it, but we need to really make
this about men,
make this about taking action,
make this about a logical framework,
make this respectable. And
if you want to be an authority in this,
and you want to
take this to the top,
you've got to think about taking this to
Piers Morgan.
You want to take this into a book.
The reason Dan Strauss was amazing
was because
he wrote a fucking book.
If you think you're going to get anywhere
with a system
that helps dudes fuck 50 chicks in a year,
you're wrong.
But the good news is you
are early enough to change the course of
this.
Otherwise,
you're going to turn into another kind of
Andrew Tate, Daniel Strauss
crossover.
But you're good in the sense
that you're there, but we've
got to tidy this up before you go
mainstream with it. So these are great.
Oh.
See,
that's a nice pic. This,
I'm really unsure of, bro.
I respect the hustle, but yeah.
And the truth is out there, men, if you're
watching, the woman out there
that wants to meet the man of her dreams,
doesn't
want to meet him on a dating app.
They want him to come chat to them in real
life.
And besides, think about this, and this
is the same with any cold approach in any
type of business, worst case scenario
is they just say no, or they can lie or
whatever.
But you turning up to a woman and saying,
"Hey, I think you're beautiful.
I'd really like your number."
If she lies to you or whatever,
you can compliment
that girl and make her day.
Just it's how you do it.
Wow,
that one took a little bit longer than
usual. Link's in the description.
If you enjoyed that,
YouTube recommends you should watch this
video that I've made
right here. But if not,
please do make sure
that you click on the links in the
description. All right. See you in a bit.
Bye-bye.